DANIEL CERÓN

REACT DEVELOPER +57 311 3979706

• DETAILS •

+57 311 3979706 desceron@unicauca.edu.co

• LINKS •

Portafolio Web

Github

LinkedIn

SKILLS

React

Git

Mysql

Firebase

typescrpt

Node

React Native

Redux

C#

Java

Flutter

JavaScript

LANGUAGES

English

Spanish

PROFILE

I am a full stack developer and future software engineer with 3 years of experience in web development. I have a solid background in frontend technologies such as React and Typescript. I also have experience in various languages and frameworks such as Dart, Flutter and React Native, as well as in backend technologies such as C#, Node.js and MySQL. I have collaborated on software development projects in a team environment, using tools such as Git and GitHub to track progress and manage code.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

FullStack Developer at ITOESTE, Argentina

November 2021 — Present

- Mysql
- React Web Apps
- React Native
- · Node is
- · git, github

Freelancer

January 2021 — Present

As a freelancer, I have assisted workers from other companies with their CSS and web3.0 work. I also have experience teaching React, Redux Thunk and other technologies to various individuals.

EDUCATION

software engineer, Universidad del Cauca

January 2018 — Present

In progress

SOLUCIONES PUBLICAS

Portfolio website

Here you can see some projects that i have made, <u>Daniel Ceron (desceron.com)</u>

B+ Tree, viewer

An application that displays a B+ tree and allows searching by nodes, <u>React App (my-page-42fc0.web.app)</u>

¶ REFERENCES

References available upon request

COURSES

React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux), Udemy January 2019 — February 2019

The Ultimate MySQL Bootcamp: Go from SQL Beginner to Expert, Udemy June 2020 — July 2020

The Git & Github Bootcamp, Udemy

August 2020 — September 2020